Oversize
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Oversize
2.1.4.2
Marist College
  Box 1569
- Oversize, 2.1.4.2
  - Lowell Thomas with unidentified man, undated; 1 (Box 1569)
    - [Lowell Thomas and four other men], 1
  - General Patton and Lowell Thomas, circa 1940s; 2 (Box 1569)
    - [General Patton, Lowell Thomas, and two other men], 1
  - Chiang Kai-shek, Lowell Thomas and General Albert C. Wedemeyer, undated; 3 (Box 1569)
    - [Chiang Kai-shek, Lowell Thomas and General Albert C. Wedemeyer], 1
  - President Herbert Hoover, undated; 4 (Box 1569)
    - [President Herbert Hoover], 1
  - Lowell Thomas and unidentified man in golf cart, undated; 5 (Box 1569)
    - [Lowell Thomas and unidentified man in golf cart], 1
  - Prosper Buranelli [sketch], undated; 6 (Box 1569)
    - [Prosper Buranelli [sketch]], 1
  - Aviator sketch by McClelland Barclay, undated; 7 (Box 1569)
    - [Aviator sketch by McClelland Barclay], 1
  - Bookie Smith about to put the arm on the Colorado Cow Man [Lowell Thomas], undated; 8 (Box 1569)
    - [Bookie Smith about to put the arm on the Colorado Cow Man (Lowell Thomas)], 1
  - General Dwight D. Eisenhower, Lowell Thomas and radio commentators, 1945; 9 (Box 1569)
    - [General Dwight D. Eisenhower, Lowell Thomas and radio commentators], 1
  - Cartoon for So Long Until Tomorrow by Lowell Thomas, circa late 1970s; 10 (Box 1569)
    - [Cartoon for So Long Until Tomorrow by Lowell Thomas], 1
  - Cartoon for So Long Until Tomorrow by Lowell Thomas, circa late 1970s; 11 (Box 1569)
    - [Cartoon for So Long Until Tomorrow by Lowell Thomas], 1
  - Publicity photograph of Lowell Thomas (Morocco), 1958; 12 (Box 1569)
    - [Publicity photograph of Lowell Thomas (Morocco)], 1
    - Note: Mary, Please have a double of this size picture made of each one so I can see - (glossy) and maybe we'll use one of them to blow up for pictures of me. It is probably one of the best I've had in quite a while so let's do something about it. L.T., 2
  - Publicity photograph of Lowell Thomas (Morocco), 1958; 13 (Box 1569)
    - [Publicity photograph of Lowell Thomas (Morocco)], 1
  - X-ray (Lowell Thomas), 1981; 14 (Box 1569)
    - Note: X-ray diagnosis page 1 [PDF], 1
    - Note: X-ray diagnosis page 2 [PDF], 2
    - Note: X-ray diagnosis page 3, 3
    - [Lowell Thomas's X-Ray], 4
  - X-ray (Lowell Thomas), 1981; 15 (Box 1569)
    - [X-ray (Lowell Thomas)], 1
  - X-ray (Lowell Thomas), 1981; 16 (Box 1569)
    - [X-ray (Lowell Thomas)], 1
  - X-ray (Lowell Thomas), 1981; 17 (Box 1569)
    - [X-ray (Lowell Thomas)], 1
  - X-ray (Lowell Thomas), 1981; 18 (Box 1569)
    - [X-ray (Lowell Thomas)], 1
  - X-ray (Lowell Thomas), 1981; 19 (Box 1569)
    - [X-ray (Lowell Thomas)], 1
  - X-ray (Lowell Thomas), 1981; 20 (Box 1569)
    - [X-ray (Lowell Thomas)], 1
  - X-ray (Lowell Thomas), 1981; 21 (Box 1569)
    - [X-ray (Lowell Thomas)], 1